I don't have to remind many Americans that the
Center for Disease Control was the one that said
you should use DDT in your homes.
Used right, it is absolutely harmless to humans
and animals.
Remember the name, DDT.
A scientific panel today reported that pesticides
may indeed represent a grave threat to mankind.
Remember the swine flu scare of 1976?
That was the year the U.S. government told us all
that swine flu could turn out to be a killer,
and Washington decided that every man, woman, and
child in the nation should get a shot to prevent a
nationwide outbreak, a pandemic.
Well, 46 million of us obediently took the shot.
Did anyone ever come to you and say there's the
possibility of neurological damage if you get into
a mass immunization program?
No.
No one ever did?
I can't believe that they would say that they did
not know that there were neurological illnesses
associated with influenza vaccination.
That simply is not true. We did know that.
And he's lying.
I guess you would have to make that assumption.
Then why does this report from your own agency
list neurological complications as a possibility?
You didn't feel it was necessary to tell the
American people that information.
Dr. Sensor's CDC also helped create the
advertising to get the public to take the shot.
The vaccines are safe, so roll up your sleeve.
And now Americans are claiming damages from Uncle
Sam amounting to three and a half billion dollars.
By far the greatest number of the claims,
two-thirds of them, are for neurological damage or
even death.
There are serious concerns tonight about how well
the CDC controls dangerous germs at its own labs
after yet another safety lapse.
For the third time in a month, the CDC
acknowledged deadly pathogens were handled
incorrectly in government labs.
That CDC is the CDC that allegedly is looking out
for your public health.